<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer Engineering Group</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/</link><description>Recent content on Computer Engineering Group</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 17:06:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.inginf.units.it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laura Nenzi</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/laura-nenzi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 17:06:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/laura-nenzi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Andrea De Lorenzo</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/andrea-de-lorenzo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 16:40:35 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/andrea-de-lorenzo/</guid><description>Andrea De Lorenzo is assistant professor at the University of Trieste. His research interests include evolutionary computation, application of machine learning techniques to engineering, computer security problems, information extraction and natural language processing.
He won the silver medal at the 13th Human-Competitive Awards, 2016, for Human-Competitive Results produced by Genetic and Evolutionary Computation.</description></item><item><title>Eric Medvet</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/eric-medvet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 16:25:31 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/eric-medvet/</guid><description>Eric Medvet is an Associate Professor in Computer Engineering at the Department of Engineering and Architecture of University of Trieste, Italy. He founded and leads the Evolutionary Robotics and Artificial Life lab (ERALlab); he is the co-founder and co-head of the Machine Learning Lab. His research activities include evolutionary computation, artificial life, embodied intelligence, and machine learning applications.</description></item><item><title>Sylvio Barbon Jr</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/sylvio-barbon-jr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:02:13 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/faculties/sylvio-barbon-jr/</guid><description>Sylvio is an Associate Professor at the Department of Engineering and Architecture at the University of Trieste (UNITS) and part of the Machine Learning Lab. Previously, he was the leader of the research group that studies machine learning at the State University of Londrina (UEL), Brazil. He received his BSc degree in Computer Science in 2005, MSc degree in Computational Physics from the University of São Paulo (2007), a degree in Computational Engineering in 2008, and PhD degree (2011) from IFSC/USP.</description></item><item><title>Cookie Policy</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/cookie-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/cookie-policy/</guid><description>This page outlines the cookie policy in use in this website along with details of cookies used by the website. This information may change over time and the latest version can be found at this page. Most websites you visit use cookies. Cookies are small text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website.</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/home/</guid><description>The Computer Engineering Group The Computer Engineering group at the University of Trieste is composed of six faculty members and a number of PhD students and research assistants.</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/cslab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/cslab/</guid><description>CSLab This is the CSLab</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/erallab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/erallab/</guid><description>EraLab This is the EraLab</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/malelab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.inginf.units.it/labs/malelab/</guid><description>MaLeLab This is the MaLeLab</description></item></channel></rss>